

James Ortiz Aldana

CR 95 70F 30 Torre 93 int 404, Medellín - Colombia

(57) 313 559 8963

james.ortiz.aldana@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/jamesd3ao

JAMES ORTIZ ALDANA SYSTEM ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

I'm a Systems Engineer with 10 years of experience in Software Development, using .Net Technologies (C#, Aspx, Sql Server, Entity Framework) and Jquery, JavaScript, Angular, Bootstrap. I'm familiarize with design patterns, software architecture, OOP. I have knowledge and experience in agile methodologies as scrum. Last years I participated in the development of software projects using .net core, angular.

SKILLS

WORK

.NET

ANGULAR

SQL SERVER

PERSONAL

COMMUNICATION

ORGANIZATION

TEAM PLAYER



SPANISH

ENGLISH



EXPERIENCE

(2011 – present)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

IPS UNIVERSITARIA

Analysis, development and management of the hospital management system of IPS Universitaria in all its layers (backEnd and frontEnd). Using technologies such as Angular, JavaScript, C# and SQL Server as a database engine.

(2011 – present)

DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR (HALFTIME)

IPS UNIVERSITARIA

Install, administration, maintain, performance monitoring and backups of copies of data the hospital databases of IPS Universitaria. Using technologies such as SQL Server as a database engine.

EDUCATION

(2005 - 2011)

SYSTEM ENGINEER

UNIVERSIDAD DE ANTIQUIA

(2019)

SCRUM MASTER

INTERNATIONAL SCRUM INSTITUTE

(2019)

SCRUM TEAM

INTERNATIONAL SCRUM INSTITUTE